本字幕仅作学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
本字幕仅作学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
==GA字幕组== 翻译：入江之鲸 冰糖 一生为白 飞行猪 开心的小末 校对：流年打死不表白 关注海燕的毯子 lynhoo00 没抢到东西的蓉小张 K在苦逼找事做 伽尘师太 字幕特效/时间轴：闹不闹得住菇 无限Boss爱渣  压制：米兰伯爵
==GA字幕组== 翻译：入江之鲸 冰糖 一生为白 飞行猪 开心的小末 校对：流年打死不表白 关注海燕的毯子 lynhoo00 没抢到东西的蓉小张 K在苦逼找事做 伽尘师太 字幕特效/时间轴：闹不闹得住菇 无限Boss爱渣  压制：米兰伯爵
All right, Ducky, I'm done.
好了 Ducky 我搞定了
Thank you, Tim.
谢谢你 Tim
You poor dear.
可怜的姑娘
Probably didn't even hear it coming.
可能根本就没听到车来的声音
Hey, where's Tony?
嘿 Tony在哪儿
I don't know.
我不知道
I offered to give him a lift,
我说我可以载他一程
but he said someone would pick him up.
但他说会有人来接他
From DC to Quantico?
从华盛顿到匡蒂科吗
Sounded strange to me, too.
我听着也觉得奇怪
I don't know how he's surviving without a car.
我真不知道 没有车他怎么活
Is that him?
是他吗
No. It's Delilah.
不 是Delilah
We're talking about sneaking away for a long weekend.
我们在计划着如何忙里偷闲度过一个美好的周末
Nice.
不错嘛
If you hens are finished,
你们两个小女生要是聊完了
I could do with some help.
就过来帮我个忙
Oh, yes.
噢 好的
Her name's Petty Officer Third Class Jody Ray.
她是海军陆战队下士 名叫Jody Ray
Patrol spotted her body just after sunrise.
巡逻队员在日出后发现了她的尸体
She works at the base clinic.
她在海军基地诊所工作
Punched out just after 21:00 last night.
昨晚九点打卡下班
And she went for a run?
然后她跑着回去吗
Coworker said she was training for a marathon.
同事说她在为马拉松做准备
Had been running almost every night for the past few months.
过去的几个月里她几乎每晚都跑步
Next of kin been notified?
通知近亲了吗?
CACO team is on it, sir.
伤亡援助电话处正在处理 先生
All right, thanks.
好的 谢谢
Nice of you to join us, DiNozzo.
很高兴你加入我们 DiNozzo
Yeah, sorry.
抱歉 来迟了
Hey, Jimmy.
嗨 Jimmy
So, what did I miss?
所以我错过了什么
Who was it that drove you all the way over here?
谁开车送你过来的
Oh.
噢
A friend.
一个朋友
No, seriously.
认真点儿
Seriously.
我是认真的
What should I do, photograph?
我该干什么 拍照吗
No, I already did it.
不 我已经拍过了
Egh. All right.
呃 好吧
Duck?
Duck
Last night, 22:00 hours,
昨晚
or thereabouts.
十点左右
Hey, Abbs.
嗨 Abbs
Come up with anything?
有什么发现
Making progress.
有进展
Look, okay, this is a part
你看
of the vehicle's headlight assembly.
这是这辆车车头灯装置的一部分
What's the make and model?
它的制造商和型号是什么
There are 47 manufacturers
在美国
of cars and trucks in the United States.
有47家小汽车和货车的制造商
Each one of those produces multiple models and body styles.
每家生产的汽车 型号和外形都多种多样
And the parts and the trim are redesigned every few years.
并且零件和外包装每隔几年就会被重新设计
There are zillions of possibilities.
因此有无限种可能
Why would anyone assume that I could take
为什么每个人都假定
a teeny, tiny piece of plastic
我能通过这小小的一块塑料
and easily identify a vehicle?
就能轻易识别出它属于哪种车
What's the make and model?
它的制造商和型号是什么
A 2003 to a 2005 Dodge Ram pickup truck.
一辆2003到2005年生产的Dodge牌敞篷载货卡车
Thank you very much.
非常感谢你
But we're going to have to narrow it down.
但是我们不得不把范围缩小
There's hundreds of trucks on that base every day.
那个基地每天都停着数百辆货车
That's what I was doing when you interrupted me.
这就是你打断我时我正在做的事
So, there was a trace of the vehicle's paint
是这样的 Ray下士手表上残留着微量的
on Petty Officer Ray's watch.
货车油漆
These are our color choices.
这是我们的颜色选项
On the top we have Inferno Red.
在最顶层我们得到了胺吸磷红
And the bottom we have Deep Molten Red.
在底层我们得到了深莫尔滕红
I don't know who comes up with these names.
我不知道谁想出了这些名字
What do you think?
你怎么认为的
I'm going to have to go with the top one.
我想我会选上面的
Agreed.
同意
So Inferno Red was only available between 2005 and 2008.
胺吸磷红在2005到2008年才有
So the only year in common between the headlight lens
因此前灯玻璃和这种颜色的油漆有交集的唯一一年
and the color is 2005.
是在2005年
Ergo we are looking for a red 2005 Dodge Ram pickup truck.
因此我们正在寻找一辆红色的2005年制造的Dodge牌敞篷载货卡车
Abby, you are the best.
Abby 你是最棒的
Still taken for granted.
这是理所当然的
Just 'cause I make it look easy doesn't mean it is.
只是因为我才让它变得简单 并不意味着它原本简单
Why do you suspect Staff Sergeant Justin Dunne?
为什么你怀疑上士Justin Dunne
Abby I.D.'d the make, model and color
Abby研究了肇事逃逸车辆的
of the hit-and-run vehicle.
型号和颜色
Only one registered on base and it belongs to Dunne.
在基地注册的车里只有一辆符合条件 它属于 Dunne
I checked the gate security footage.
我检查了门卫的摄像头画面
His truck never left Quantico last night.
他的货车昨晚根本没有离开过匡蒂科
What do we know about him? Single.
我们知道他的哪些信息 单身
Joined the Corps right out of high school.
高中一毕业就入伍了
He's a helo mechanic.
他是个直升机机械师
Scheduled to deploy on an LHA
本周晚些时候将被部署到
to the Med, later this week.
去往地中海的两栖攻击舰服役
And most pertinent...
还有最相关的
he has a DUI in his past.
他有过酒驾史
Bring him in.
把他带进来
I love it when it all comes together so quickly.
我很高兴一切进展得这么快
Not me. Makes me nervous.
我不这么认为 反而会很担心
Too easy.
这也太简单了
Let's go.
走吧
You ever going to get a new car?
你没想过要买辆新车吗
Well, firstly, I never buy new cars.
第一 我从来不买新车
Secondly, I need something that ignites my passions.
第二我需要能点燃我的激情的东西
It's like a woman.
它就像女人
I need to be in love before I commit.
在我做出承诺前我要爱上它
You've never committed to a woman.
你从来没对女人做出过承诺
Sergeant Dunne. NCIS.
Dunne上士 我们是海军罪案调查处
Sergeant Dunne!
Dunne上士
Freeze. NCIS.
别动 海军罪案调查处
Yeah, that's my truck, but
是 这是我的货车 但是
I swear, I don't know how it got that way.
我发誓 我不知道它怎么会跑那去了
You didn't drive it last night? No.
你昨晚没开它吗 没有
I haven't used the truck in a couple of days.
我已经好几天没用过那辆车了
How do you get to work? I walk. Need the exercise.
那你怎么去上班 我步行去 就当是锻炼
The maintenance bay isn't that far from my quarters.
维修处所在的海湾离我的住处并不远
Where were you last night, 22:00 hours?
昨晚十点你在哪
I was in my room... asleep.
我在我的房间里...睡觉
Had a tough week.
经历了艰难的一周
I was exhausted.
我精疲力竭
You sure you weren't drunk
你确定你不是因为喝高了
and you just don't remember what you did?
而忘记了自己做了些什么吧
We know about your DUI.
我们知道你曾酒驾
I've been sober for 13 months.
我头脑清醒了13个月了
I go to three or four meetings a week.
我每周有三到四次会议
So, if you weren't driving the pickup and you're innocent,
好吧 如果车不是你开的 你是无辜的
why were you climbing out a window?
为什么你要爬窗户逃走
I know my rights.
我知道我的权利
I'm not saying any more until I have a lawyer.
在我的律师来之前我什么也不会说的
Okay.
好得
Then you can have the lawyer of your choice
接下来你可以自己选一个律师了
or JAG will assign one to you.
或者军法处长给你指派一个
Hey, McGee.
嗨 McGee
Did you bring me Sergeant Dunne's right boot?
Dunne上士的右脚上的靴子你带过来了吗
Sorry, Abbs, he lawyered up and didn't give a permissive search.
抱歉 Abbs 他请了律师 限制了我们的调查
Hmm. Well, did you get a good look at his feet?
好吧 那你有没有好好看一看他的右脚
Huh? Well, the footprint that you cast
啊 犯罪现场留下的脚印
at the crime scene, it's a standard-issue Marine Corps
那是海军陆战队标准
combat boot, size ten and a half.
战斗靴 尺码是十英寸半
Well, I guess he might wear that size.
我猜他可能也穿那个码
It's well worn and has a very distinctive gash
靴子穿了很久了 在右脚跟
in the right heel.
有一个非常好辨认的切口
I'd just really love to match it to Sergeant Dunne.
我希望犯罪现场的鞋印能和Dunne上士的靴子相吻合
Well, you're going to have to wait till morning.
这样啊 那你就只能等到明天了
Any luck here?
这里有什么发现么
Oh, this is definitely the pickup truck.
哦 这绝对是肇事逃逸的那辆货车
The tires match the tracks that were in the dirt.
货车的轮胎符合犯罪现场留下的轮胎印
And I got hair, blood and clothing fibers
我还在车头找到了头发 血迹和衣服上的纤维
off the front end that match our victim.
能和被害人的特征相匹配
So, I'll get DNA confirmation in the morning,
就这样 我明天就能拿到DNA确认单
and we should have it locked up.
我们现在先把这辆车锁起来
Great.
很好
Hey, have you been giving Tony rides to work
对了 自Tony的车撞毁了后
since his car was wrecked?
你有没有开车送他上班么
No.
没有
Hmm.
哦
Somebody dropped him off
今天早上有人开车
all the way out at Quantico this morning.
一路把他送到了匡蒂科
Is he dating someone?
莫非他在和某人约会
Oh... I don't think so.
哦 我不这么想
Hmm.
哦
You always smell so great.
你的味道总是那么好闻
Let me guess-- you missed the sexual harassment meeting
我猜你又一次错过了今年的
again this year.
"防止职场性骚扰"讲座
Hey, everybody, look who I found in the lobby.
嘿 伙计们 快看我在休息室里发现了谁
Hey, Clark.
嘿 Clark
- Hey, guys. - Morning, Carrie.
-大家好 -早啊 Carrie
I don't think I've had the pleasure.
我似乎还没有这个荣幸
Dr. Mallard,
这位是Mallard医生
meet former FBI agent Carrie Clark.
这位是前FBI探员 Carrie Clark
Now in private law practice.
现在在私营法律事务所任职
Nice to meet you, Doctor.
很高兴认识你 医生
- Likewise. - Carrie worked
-我也是 -Carrie在几年前的港务局案中
the Norfolk side of the Port Authority case
负责诺福克海军基地那边的事务 【注：Norfolk是美国最大的海军基地 绝大部分舰艇都是在这里生产的】
a few years ago, made Fornell look good.
使Fornell脸上大为增光
It was a tough job.
这可不是个容易的活儿
No, you guys made it easy.
你们帮了不少忙
I don't remember that case.
我不记得那个案子了
Grand theft, Ducky,
是个巨额财产盗窃案 Ducky
no autopsy, no body, no you.
没有尸体 无须尸检 所以你没参与
Ah.
原来如此
What brings you to NCIS?
是谁把你带到NCIS来的
I'm here to see Sergeant Dunne.
我是来见Dunne上士的
You're his lawyer?
你是他的律师
- Say it ain't so. - Yes, where is he?
-告诉我这不是真的 -我是 他在哪里 【Say it ain`t so是1988年上映的美国体育电影《八面威风》中的经典台词】
Staff Sergeant Dunne's in a holding cell across the yard.
Dunne上士在院子那端的拘留所里
Agent McGee can take you to him.
McGee探员会带你过去
Thank you.
多谢
Good to see you guys.
很高兴见到大家
- Bye. - Duck,
-再见 -Duck
you can release Petty Officer Ray's body any time
你随时可以移交
you're ready.
Ray下士的尸体
You notice anything different about Carrie, boss?
你注意到Carrie有什么不同了吗 老大
No wedding ring.
婚戒不在了
Told you the husband was a handbag.
跟你说过 她丈夫就是个手提包
Handbag?
手提包
Something useless you hang on your arm.
挎在手臂上的没用的东西
Oh.
噢
Hey, Agent Fornell, it's DiNozzo.
嘿 Fornell探员 我是DiNozzo
Listen, can you give me the skinny
关于那位美丽动人的Carrie Clark
on the ever-fetching Carrie Clark?
你能告诉我一些小道消息么
Hello.
你好
I'm Carrie Clark.
我是Carrie Clark
Didn't expect you to look like you do.
没想到你长得这么漂亮
Is that a problem?
有什么问题吗
Not if you're as good as my cousin said.
要是你像我表哥说的那么优秀 就没问题
Well, I haven't had any complaints.
目前还没有任何投诉
You're about to be arraigned on some very serious charges.
你即将因为一些非常严重的指控而被提审
I don't know anything about a hit-and-run.
关于这个逃逸事件 我什么都不知道
If it was my pickup, someone else was driving.
如果真是我的皮卡车的话 也不是我在驾驶
Any idea who?
你觉得是谁在开车
Justin, I want to believe you, but you seem very nervous.
Justin 我想要相信你 但你看起来非常不安
Is there something that you want to tell me?
有什么想告诉我的吗
Where were you at 10:00 last night?
昨晚十点你在哪里
Doesn't matter.
有什么关系
Of course it does.
当然有关系
- I have an alibi. - Okay.
-我有不在场证明 -好
That's all you need to know.
你就需要知道这些
Are you going to tell me?
你要告诉我吗
All right, if that is going to be your attitude,
好吧 如果你是这种态度
how about I save you some money?
我来给你省点钱吧
JAG will assign someone to you for free.
军法署会为你安排一位免费律师
Hold on.
等一下
Could this room be bugged?
这间屋子可能被监听吗
No, no way-- that would be illegal.
不 不会的 那是违法的
Are you recording our conversation?
你在录音我们的谈话吗
No.
没有
You're my lawyer.
你是我的律师
Anything I say, you can't tell anyone?
无论我说了什么 你都不能告诉任何人 是吗
It's called attorney-client privilege.
这叫做"律师-当事人保密特权"
Everything that you say is confidential.
你所说的一切 我都会保密
It doesn't leave this room unless you want it to.
除非你授权 这些谈话不会被泄露
Rules of ethics prohibit me
职业道德不允许我
from telling anyone what we discuss.
将所讨论的内容告知任何人
You sure?
你能保证吗
I promise you, Justin.
我向你保证 Justin
When that girl was killed,
那个女孩被杀时
I was 35 miles away in Falls Church.
我在35英里外的福尔斯彻奇市 【注：维吉尼亚州的一个城市】
And what were you doing there?
你在那里做什么
Stabbing a guy to death.
捅死一个人
Why are you checking airline schedules?
你干嘛要查看航班时刻表
Miami?
迈阿密
Do you have to know everything?
你必须要知道所有事情吗
Yes, it's in my DNA.
是的 好奇是我的本性
Well, you're gonna drive me crazy until I tell you, so...
如果我不告诉你的话 你会把我给逼疯的 所以...
Things are quiet here, this case is wrapping up.
这里没什么事情了 案子也快结束了
I've got a few vacation days coming,
接下来我会有几天的休假
so Delilah and I have been talking
Delilah和我商量着
about getting away for a long weekend.
打算离开这里 共度一个长周末
McGee, I'm impressed.
McGee 真让我刮目相看啊
Miami, South Beach, hot clubs, stone crabs.
迈阿密 南海滩 酒吧 石头蟹
It is unlike you.
真不像你的风格
I knew I shouldn't have said anything.
我就知道我不该告诉你
Oh.
噢
That didn't take long.
没花多长时间啊
Your client come to his senses?
你的委托人醒悟了吗
Wants to confess?
想要坦白吗
No.
不
Wants to make a deal, then?
那么是想要做个交易吗
Sergeant Dunne says he's innocent.
Dunne上士说他是无辜的
Innocent?
无辜
We've forensically tied his pickup to the victim.
我们有证据证明 他的皮卡车与受害人相关联
He ran when we tried to question him.
我们去问他问题的时候 他试图逃跑
He claims he has an alibi.
他声称他有不在场证明
Well, what is it? We'll check it out.
那么证明是什么 我们会确认一下
Well, it is not that simple, Gibbs,
事情没那么简单 Gibbs
he told me in confidence.
他是在保密的情况下告诉我的
It's privileged.
这是机密信息
If he doesn't want to tell you himself,
如果他不想自己告诉你的话
then my hands are tied.
我也束手无策
We've got 48 hours to either charge him or let him go.
我们有48个小时 来决定是指控他或者释放他
Give us something.
给我们一些信息
All right, listen, I will go check out his alibi myself
这样吧 我自己去调查他的不在场证明
and I will get back to you.
然后我再来找你
The guy's facing vehicular homicide
这家伙面对车祸致人死命罪
and hit-and-run charges.
以及肇事逃逸的指控
He won't use an alibi?
却不肯提供不在场证明
Is he crazy?
他疯了吗
Abbs.
Abbs
Gibbs... you're amazing.
Gibbs 你太了不起了
How did you know that someone else was driving the truck?
你是怎么知道是其他人在开车
What'd you find?
你发现了什么
Well, it's more what I didn't find that's interesting.
是我没发现的那部分更有趣
I mean, before you called, I was just trying
在你打电话之前 我只是试图
to match the victim to the vehicle, which I did.
将受害者与车辆联系起来 而且我的确做到了
- But? - But then, when you asked me
-但是 -但是当你问我
if there's a chance that someone
有没有可能
other than the owner of the truck was driving,
是非车主的其他人在驾驶时
I dusted the whole thing for prints, I didn't find any.
我在整辆车上搜寻指纹 可是什么都没有找到
- Just Staff Sergeant Dunne's? - No.
-所以只有Dunne上士的指纹吗 -不
I mean, like none, nada, zip, zilch, nothing.
我是说 无 没 零 空 啥也没有
Almost the entire surface of the truck
基本上这辆车的整个表面
was wiped clean of fingerprints--
都被擦去了指纹的痕迹
the door handle, the steering wheel, the gearshift,
门把手 方向盘 档位
the seat adjuster, everything.
座椅调节器 所有地方
Now, I got reminded o-of my Uncle Horace.
这让我想起了我的Horace叔叔
He was always losing things
他总是丢三落四的
like his glasses and his wallet and his keys.
比如他的眼镜 钱包 钥匙
He got locked out of his own car so many times
他好几次都被锁在自己的车外
that he, he hid a key on his car.
所以他在车上藏了一把钥匙
And then I found... this...
于是我发现了这个
...under the front wheel well.
就藏在前轮圈下面
Wiped clean?
被擦干净了么
Oh, yeah, including the key inside.
没错 包括其中的钥匙
That is hardly something that the owner would do.
车主不可能做出这种事情
Someone else was driving the truck.
是其他人在驾驶这辆车
Yes, and they tried to make it look like they weren't.
对 而且他们还试图掩盖痕迹
Thanks, Abbs.
谢了 Abbs
I don't understand why people run.
我不理解人为什么要跑
Oh, well, it's therapeutic,
跑步很有疗效
it has great cardiovascular benefits.
对心血管问题有极大的益处
What's more, it gets the old endorphins pumping.
而且还会刺激内啡肽分泌 【注：又称安多芬 有镇痛及保持快乐的功能】
I'll tell you, running gives me a great high.
我跟你说 跑步让我十分兴奋
I was referring to the driver
我是说那个司机
running from the scene of the accident, Mr. Palmer.
为什么要从肇事现场逃逸 Palmer先生
Oh, yes, yes.
噢 对 没错
Did you know that pedestrian hit-and-runs are
你知道吗 这个国家目前涉及行人的肇事逃逸
at an epidemic rate in this country?
比例前所未有之高
Nearly 11%
在美国发生的
of all traffic accidents in the United States are
所有交通事故中 有百分之十一
hit-and-runs.
是肇事逃逸
That Petty Officer Ray?
那是Ray下士吗
Yes.
是的
Hold on to the body for a little while longer,
把这个尸体留得久一点
will you, Duck?
可以吗 Duck
You signed the release.
你签署了尸体移交文件
Has something changed?
有什么变化吗
Yeah.
是的
But I don't know what.
但我还不知道是什么
Yeah, it's Gibbs.
喂 我是Gibbs
Hi, it's Carrie Clark.
Hi 我是Carrie Clark
Yeah, Carrie, what do you got?
好的 Carrie 你查到什么
Well, Dunne's alibi
是这样的 Dunne的不在场证明
checks out, it's solid.
查清楚了 非常可靠
Mm-hmm, tell me. I can't.
嗯 告诉我 我不能
You're going to have to start looking
你们得开始寻找
for the real hit-and-run driver because it's not my client.
真正的逃逸肇事司机 因为他不是我的委托人
Carrie, look, I can't just take your word for it, okay?
Carrie 听着 我不能仅凭你的话来判断 好吗
Give me something here.
告诉我一些线索
You're gonna have to figure this one out on your own, Gibbs.
你必须自己解决这事 Gibbs
Jethro, is something wrong?
Jethro 出什么问题了吗
Looks like you won't be leaving us today after all,
看起来你今天终究是不能离开我们了
my dear.
亲爱的
McGee,
McGee,
trace the last call, will you?
追踪最后一通电话 可以吗
You want me to find out who it was from?
你想要我查出是谁打的
It was from Carrie Clark.
是Carrie Clark打的
Usually her name comes up on that little window there.
通常她的名字都会在屏幕上显示出来
This time it didn't; it was just a number.
但这一次没有 那里只显示了一个数字
Hmm.
嗯
What did she say?
她说了什么
Said her client's alibi checked out.
说她委托人的不在场证明已经核实
I don't believe it.
我不相信
Well, the number belongs to a pay phone.
好吧 这个数字属于一个投币电话
Pay phone?
投币电话
I didn't think there were any left.
我还以为它们都销声匿迹了呢
325 Acacia Avenue in Falls Church.
325 金合欢街 福尔斯彻奇市
It's in front of the library.
就在一个图书馆前面
Carrie has a cell.
Carrie有手机
Why would she use a pay phone?
为什么她要用投币电话
Not sure.
不知道
She knows her client's alibi.
她知道她委托人的不在场证明
She knows she can't tell us.
她也知道她不能告诉我们
What are you thinking, boss?
你认为怎样呢 老大
Carrie knows we'll be intrigued,
Carrie知道我们会对此感兴趣
she knows that we'll trace the call.
她知道我们会追踪这通电话
Did she just drop a bread crumb?
她是不是特地给我们留了条线索
Yeah. Go. Go on.
是的 去 快过去
There's the pay phone.
就是那个投币电话
Why was Carrie calling from here?
为什么Carrie要从这里打
Library, hardware store?
图书馆 五金商店
Oh, there we go, Great Sexpectations.
哦 就是那了 性用品商品
I seriously doubt it, Tony.
我对此深表怀疑 Tony
Hey, there's a squad car.
嘿 那里有一辆警察巡逻车
Yeah, let's check it out.
是的 让我们过去问问
Did you ever find out if Carrie was divorced?
你可曾查出Carrie是否离婚了
Ah. Trial separation.
啊 暂时分居
She's not wearing her ring.
她没有带结婚戒指
You know what that means.
你知道这代表什么
It's over.
这段感情结束了
Hey.
嘿
NCIS.
NCIS
Special Agents DiNozzo and McGee.
特别探员DiNozzo和McGee
Dockry, Homicide.
Dockry 凶案组
Homicide?
凶案组
What are you guys up to?
你们来这里干嘛
Oh, just pounding the pavement, boring Navy stuff.
哦 只是在街头徘徊 枯燥无味
Yeah, nothing serious like homicide.
是的 不像凶杀案那么严肃认真
Who's dead?
谁死了
Store owner-- Donny Sullivan.
商店的店主――Donny Sullivan
Stabbed to death night before last.
前天晚上被人刺死
Body was found in the upstairs residence yesterday morning by an employee.
尸体是一个员工昨天早上在楼上的住处发现的
Any leads? Nothing concrete yet.
有头绪吗 没有什么具体的
Anything I can help you guys with?
我能帮你们什么忙吗
Ah, no, we got to go.
哦 不 我们得走了
He gets hungry.
他很饿了
It's true. See you around.
没错 回头见
Hey, do you guys know a Special Agent Gibbs?
嘿 你们认识特别探员Gibbs吗?
Oh, yeah, we affectionately refer to him as "boss."
哦 是的 我们亲切地称呼他为"老大"
Tell him Hickory's son said hi.
告诉他Hickory的儿子向他问好
Hickory?
Hickory
He'll know.
他会明白的
The storekeeper's murder happened about the same time as the hit-and-run.
商店店主的谋杀案大致和肇事逃逸发生在同一时间
Think this has something to do with Dunne's alibi?
你认为这件事情和Dunne的不在场证明有关
If Dunne was involved, then how'd he get from Quantico to here and back?
如果Dunne参与了这件凶案 那么他是怎么在匡蒂科和这里来回的
His truck never left the base.
他的卡车从来没有离开过基地
I think your amorous little weekend in Miami just went bye-bye.
我觉得你的迈阿密激情周末刚刚跟你说再见了
Yeah. Gibbs. Hey, boss.
是的 Gibbs 嘿 老大
We might have a lead on Dunne's alibi.
我们在Dunne的不在场证明上也许有线索了
Find out what you can-- discreetly, DiNozzo.
尽可能查出你能查到的--小心行事 DiNozzo
Gibbs, Gibbs, Gibbs, so I told you that I dusted
Gibbs Gibbs Gibbs 如之前我告诉过你的那样我想擦拭
the entire truck for prints, but I didn't.
整辆卡车便于查找指纹 但是我没有
I only dusted the places that a person would touch,
我只擦了会被触摸的地方
and then I realized that if someone's going
随后我意识到如果有人想要
to adjust the seat lever, which they did,
调整座位的高低 那样的话
they would probably also adjust the rearview mirror.
也很有可能调整后视镜
And guess what I found--
猜猜我发现了什么--
a fresh right thumbprint on its backside.
在后视镜的后面采集到一枚新鲜的右手拇指指纹
Thumbprint have a name?
拇指指纹有名字吗
Don't be silly, Gibbs,
别傻了 Gibbs
thumbprints don't have names.
拇指指纹怎么可能有名字呢
People do.
人才有
My first pass was to run it against all the personnel at Quantico.
我第一时间将它和所有在匡蒂科的人的指纹作对比
And that's all I had to do.
于是这便是所有我要做的事情了
Private Daniel Cliff.
二等兵Daniel Cliff
Gibbs will be in, in a minute.
Gibbs很快就会过来
Thank you.
谢谢你
You know why they brought me over here?
你知道他们为什么带我来这里吗
No.
不知道
I told them I wouldn't say anything else until my lawyer was present.
我告诉他们除非我律师在场 否则我一句话也不会说
Well, I checked your alibi.
是的 我核实过你的不在场证明
You weren't lying.
你没有撒谎
Hey, you don't know who's on the other side of that glass.
嘿 你不知道玻璃的另一边都有谁
Let's not discuss it again.
咱们就不要再讨论这个问题了
You know all you have to.
你知道所有你需要做的
I'm innocent.
我是无辜的
Couldn't this have waited till the morning?
就不能等到早上吗
Nope.
不能
You know him? Yeah,
你认识他吗 是的
Private Cliff-- I see him around.
二等兵Cliff--我见过他
You two close?
你们俩关系很好
No.
不
We hung a couple of times back when I was drinking.
我们一起出去喝过几次酒
That was a long time ago.
那是很久很久以前了
Have you seen each other lately?
最近你们有见过面吗
Run into him in the laundry, rec room, that's it.
在洗衣店 娱乐室 见过他 就这些
You give Private Cliff permission
你同意让二等兵Cliff
to drive your pickup truck?
开你的小型轻便卡车
Hell, no.
去你的 当然没有
What was that about?
这是怎么回事
Gibbs? Sounds like you have a suspect for your hit-and-run.
Gibbs 看来你的肇事逃逸案子已经有了一个嫌疑犯
You gonna let my client go? Not yet.
能让我的委托人离开吗？还不行
Come on. He's due to deploy.
拜托 他在这里仅仅是因为配合你们
Haven't brought Private Cliff in for questioning yet.
还没有把二等兵Cliff带过来问话
Well, your 48-hour clock is ticking.
好吧 你的48小时时间快到了
If you don't charge my client by tomorrow,
如果你明天之前还不指控我的委托人
you have to let him go.
那你就必须让他走
You know, a funny thing happened.
你知道的 一些有趣的事情刚刚发生
We got a tip.
我们得到了一个线索
Sent us to a cigar store in Falls Church.
指引我们去了一家在福尔斯彻奇市的雪茄店
Really?
真的吗
Yeah, it was a crime scene, a homicide.
是的 那是个犯罪现场 凶杀案
If your client wasn't driving his truck on base the other night,
如果你的委托人那晚没有在基地开着他的卡车
could he have been in Falls Church?
那他会不会在福尔斯彻奇市呢
My only concern is Sergeant Dunne's rights.
我只关心Dunne上士的权利
He wasn't involved in the hit-and-run.
他没有参与这起肇事逃逸案件
Hmm.
嗯
A non-denial denial.
非否认的否认
Jason Robards, as Ben Bradlee in All the President's Men.
就像Jason Robards在惊天大阴谋里扮演的Ben Bradlee一样
She didn't say "no."
她没有说"不"
Oh, you're crazy.
哦 你真是疯了
No, you must need glasses.
不 你肯定需要眼镜了
Yeah, yeah. All right, later.
是的是的 好吧 晚点再聊
What's so funny?
什么那么好笑
That was Hollander in HR.
人力资源部的Hollander
She claims that she saw you this morning
她声称今天早上看到你
at the front gate getting off a city bus.
在一辆公交车的前门下车
Yeah, that was me.
是的 那是我
Listen, I know I made fun of you in the past for riding the bus,
听着 我知道我曾经因为你乘公交车开过你玩笑
but I have to admit I was wrong.
但我必须承认我错了
I've been using public transportation,
我这段时间一直乘坐公共交通
and I really like it.
而且我真的很喜欢
You're kidding. No.
你在开玩笑 不
I have time to read,
那样我可以有时间去读书
make some calls and, best of all...
打一些电话 最重要的是...
I get to watch people.
我可以观察人们
People are fascinating.
人类是如此地令人神魂颠倒
Okay, Tony, I'm...
好吧 Tony 我...
I don't even know what I am right now.
就算我不知道我自己现在是什么
But I know you, and this is not you.
但是我懂你 而且我知道这不是你
Boss, I went through Sergeant Dunne's e-mails,
老大 我检查了Dunne上士的所有电子邮件
phone calls and credit cards.
电话和信用卡
I came up empty.
什么都没查到
There's no connecting him to the dead cigar-store owner.
他和那个死去的雪茄店老板没有任何关系
What would his motive be to kill the guy?
他杀那人的动机是什么
Did find out Dunne exchanged a lot of calls with a Maryland cell phone number.
但我却发现Dunne给一个马里兰州的电话号码打了很多次
Belongs to an Olivia Chandler.
电话号码属于一个Olivia Chandler的人
Yeah, well, find out who she is.
是的 好吧 查出她是谁
Yup.
是的
Hmm. Do we dare run Sergeant Dunne's name by Falls Church PD,
嗯 我们能否大胆运用福尔斯彻奇市警察局的资料库搜索一下Dunne上士的名字
see if they can make a connection?
也许我们能够找到他们之间的联系
Can't do that.
不能这么做
Got to protect Carrie Clark.
我们要保护Carrie Clark
You can do it off the record.
你可以暗地里做
The homicide detective in charge seemed to know you.
那个负责凶杀案的警探似乎认识你
Who? Well, he said to tell you,
谁 额 他说告诉你
"Hickory's son says hello."
"Hickory'的儿子向你问好"
That's Paul Dockry.
那是Paul Dockry
Hickory Dickory Dockry.
Hickory Dickory Dockry
His dad and I were in the Corps together.
他老爸和我在同一个陆战队
Come on, DiNozzo. You're with me.
快来 DiNozzo 你跟着我
Huh. People are fascinating.
哈 人类真是令人神魂颠倒
This boot print was found at a crime scene
这枚靴子的印记是在犯罪现场找到的
that killed a petty officer.
杀害了一名下士
This is the same boot, the same cutout at the right heel.
你的靴子 跟肇事车辆右轮胎上的抠图吻合
And you know what else, Cliff?
你知道 我们还掌握了什么吗 Cliff？
We got your thumbprint on the rearview mirror
我们在卡车后视镜上发现了
of that vehicle.
你的拇指指纹
What happened?
到底发生了什么事情？
It was dark.
当时天很黑
I couldn't see her until it was too late.
等我看到她的时候 一切都晚了
What were you doing with Staff Sergeant Dunne's truck?
你开着Dunne上士的卡车干什么？
I had a few drinks.
我喝了几杯
I know this girl in Stafford.
我认识斯塔福德的这个女孩
I overheard Dunne in the rec room.
我无意间听Dunne在录音室提过
Said he had a rough week and was gonna hit the rack early.
他说这星期很累 会早点睡觉
Figured I'd take his truck and be back
我觉得可以开他的车子
before he even missed it. Bull!
在他发现之前 就能赶回来的 屁话
How'd you know about the hidden key?
你是怎么知道车子外藏着钥匙？
About a year ago, when he was still drinking,
大概一年前 他当时还在酗酒
he got wasted, locked himself out of his truck.
他昏昏沉沉 把自己锁在了车子外边
Got the hidden key out, had me drive him home.
于是他找到藏着的车钥匙 让我送他回家
You left an injured woman to die by the side of the road?
你就眼睁睁 把一个受伤的女性扔在路边等死？
No!
不！
I stopped.
我停下车了
I knew she was dead,
我知道她已经死了
and I realized how bad it all looked.
然后意识到这一切看起来有多糟
I was drinking, I was driving a stolen vehicle.
我当时喝醉了 还开着一辆偷来的车
I just panicked and drove back to the parking lot.
我慌了 然后赶快把车开回停车场
You got to believe me.
你得相信我的话
It was an accident.
这只是个意外
I'll book him. Uh-uh.
我来钉死他 哼
If we charge Private Cliff
如果我们起诉 Private Cliff
with the hit-and-run,
犯了肇事逃逸罪
we got to let Staff Sergeant Dunne go.
我们就得释放 Dunne上士
I'm not ready to do that.
而我并不准备这样做
We only have a few more hours
只剩几小时
until the clock runs out on Dunne.
法定羁押Dunne上士的时间就到了
Put him in a holding cell.
把他关进牢房
Hey, Paul. Hey, Gibbs.
-你好 Paul -你好 Gibbs
Sorry. Just give me a sec.
抱歉 等我一会
I got to finish this text to my daughter.
我得给女儿发完短信
Only way she'll communicate me.
这是她跟我交流的唯一方式
The kid never answers her phone.
这孩子从来不接电话
Been a long time.
好久不见
How's your dad?
令尊怎么样了？
Stubborn as always.
老顽固
Thought I might run into you at my kid sister's wedding.
我以为会在我妹妹的婚礼上碰到你
Oh, no, no. I'm not... I'm not big on weddings.
哦 不 我对婚礼不感冒
I can understand that.
我理解
Thanks for meeting me.
谢谢你能见我
Yeah. I ran into your agents in Falls Church.
嗯 我在福尔彻奇市碰见了你的探员
Taking it, that wasn't a coincidence.
我断定 那可不是巧合
Uh, no. So,
哦 不是吧
what's your interest in my homicide?
你对我的谋杀案有什么兴趣？
Well, it's complicated, messy.
呃 说起来复杂了 一团糟
Following a lead.
我们追查线索的时候
Holding someone on an unrelated charge.
扣押了一个跟罪行无关的人
Seems to have an alibi,
看似有不在场证明
but he may have been involved with your dead storekeeper
但是他貌似跟你的死亡店主有关系
Like to talk to him. Can't let you, not yet.
-很乐意跟他聊聊 -现在还不行
Still trying to protect a source.
我们还在保护信息来源
You have him in custody.
目前你扣押了他
Yeah, for the time being.
对 目前扣押了他
What can you tell me about your case?
关于你的案子 你能跟我分享点什么？
Discovered Sullivan was a bookie.
我们发现Sullivan是个赌徒
Used the cigar store as a front.
用香烟店做幌子
Guy you holding like to gamble?
你们羁押的人 看上去是个赌徒？
I'll find out.
我会查明白的
You got any suspects for the murder?
你们现在有嫌疑人吗？
Yes... and no.
有...也没有
Loser with a mile-long rap sheet, Wendell Kaiser.
劣迹斑斑的监狱常客 Wendell Kaiser
Into Sullivan big-time.
对Sullivan不满已久了
Very public arguments.
双方公然的争吵过
Kaiser even makes threats.
Kaiser甚至威胁过死者
However, airtight alibi.
然而 Kaiser有无懈可击的不在场证明
In New York at the time of the murder.
谋杀案发生的时候 他正在纽约
Just got back this morning. Hmm.
今天早上才回来 嗯
Maybe alibis are in season, huh?
也许现在很流行不在场证明 哈？
Okay.
好的
Cheeseburger,
干酪汉堡
no dressing, fries.
不加配料的炸薯条
Did I miss something? You didn't even order.
我错过什么了？ 你根本没点菜
Well, he doesn't have to.
哦 他不需要开口点菜
Thanks, Elaine.
谢谢你 Elaine
Can you, uh, get me Kaiser's file?
嗯 你能把Kaiser的档案给我吗？
Sure.
当然可以
I'll e-mail you the highlights.
我会把要点 发到你邮箱
Your guy wouldn't happen to be a hit man for hire, would he?
你们羁押的那个人 不会碰巧就是受雇的职业杀手吧
No. I don't think so.
不 我觉得不是
What? Need something?
怎么了？ 需要点什么？
Yeah, a knife to cut this beast.
嗯 我需要一把刀来切下汉堡
That'll work.
不错
No, no, no.
不 不 不
You're not serious.
你在开玩笑吧
There's no way she's married to him.
她怎么可能嫁给他呢
Almost five years.
他们结婚差不多5年了
The very definition of a trophy wife.
再次诠释了什么叫做花瓶妻子
What you looking at? Olivia Chandler.
-你在看什么？-Olivia Chandler
The woman who Sergeant Dunne
跟Dunne上士
has been exchanging texts and calls with.
发短信 打电话的女人
That little man
那个糟老头
must have a big,
肯定非常
big... bank account. She's married to him.
-非常有钱 -她嫁给他
They live together in Chevy Chase Village.
一起住在切维蔡斯村
Very la-dee-dah.
世界无比精彩
Only thing on her record is a DUI.
她的唯一违规记录是酒后驾车
She was picked up for driving erratically in her Aston Martin.
交警发现她的时候 她正开着阿斯顿马丁横冲直撞
So many jokes.
太搞笑了
Of course she drives an Aston Martin.
（她那么有钱 ）肯定开的是阿斯顿丁
When I was searching traffic cameras
当我搜索有没有交通摄像头
to see if I could place Dunne anywhere near the cigar store
拍到谋杀案当晚
the night of the murder,
Dunne上士在香烟商店附近出现
I found something interesting.
我找到一些有趣的东西
Olivia Chandler's car.
我发现了Olivia Chandler的汽车
Now, this was taken a block from the cigar store.
这张照片是在距离香烟店一个街区的地方拍的
Because of the tinted windows,
由于车窗颜色
you can't make out who's inside.
所以没法确定车里都有谁
I sent it to Abby.
我把照片发给了Abby
It's a long shot, but maybe she can enhance the image.
距离很远 不过她或许能够增强一下图像
Sullivan was a bookie.
Sullivan是个赌徒
Falls Church police had a suspect,
福尔彻奇市警方有一个嫌疑犯
but he has an alibi.
但是他有不在场证明
Detective Dockry said he was going to e-mail the file.
Dockry探长说他会把嫌犯的档案发到我邮箱
He did.
他已经发了
Wendell Kaiser. McGee--
Wendell Kaiser McGee
see if Staff Sergeant Dunne had a gambling problem
你查一下 Dunne上士有没有赌博的习惯
or any connection to this guy.
或者是跟这个人的任何联系
DiNozzo...
DiNozzo...
check out Olivia Chandler.
查一下Olivia Chandler.
With pleasure.
很高兴 接受任务
Thank you, boss.
谢谢你 老大
May I help you?
有什么我能帮你的
Oh, I hope so.
噢 我希望你能帮我呢
NCIS Special Agent Anthony DiNozzo.
NCIS特别探员Anthony DiNozzo
NCIS
NCIS？
I love this car. It's smoking hot.
我喜欢这辆车 它真火辣
I'm in the market myself.
我目前在汽车市场里
Between vehicles right now.
我有选择障碍
Terrible gas mileage, but that's what James Bond drives.
名车耗油量大 但是詹姆斯邦德也开这样的车 （我总觉得Tony在含沙射影说olivia，你们怎么看）
Did you know that?
你知道这个事实吗
I have no idea. What do you want?
我不清楚  你来这干什么
Oh, we're investigating a Marine.
噢 我们在调查一名海军军官
Staff Sergeant Justin Dunne.
Justin Dunne上士
How do you know him?
你是怎么认识他的
-I don't. -Really?
-我不认识他 -真的吗？
'Cause you exchanged a lot of calls with him,
你跟他可是打过不少电话
and that would suggest otherwise.
这就说明你认识他啊
We met at an A.A. meeting.
我们在一次匿名戒酒会上认识的 【A.A：Alcoholics Anonymous:匿名戒酒会】
We talk to each other for support.
我们彼此相互支持
Sobriety is an ongoing battle.
保持清醒是个持久战
So why'd you say you didn't know him?
那你为什么说不认识他
The second "A" in A.A. is for "anonymous."
因为 匿名戒酒会的成员对外保持匿名
I shouldn't be talking about him or anyone else.
我不应该在这谈论他和其他人
Gotcha.
明白了
So you're taking a little trip?
所以你这是要出门旅行吗
I'm going to Jamaica with some girlfriends.
我跟几个女性朋友去牙买加
Yeah, mon. Jamaica.
噢 牙买加
Well, have yourself a nice time.
祝你玩得愉快
Did you connect Staff Sergeant Dunne to the dead bookie
你找到Dunne上士和死去的赌徒
or the Falls Church suspect?
或者和福尔斯彻奇案子嫌疑人的联系了吗
No, not yet.
还没有
Based on the people I've talked to,
根据我问过的人所说的来看
it appears that Dunne's not a gambler.
Dunne似乎并不是一个赌徒
I still have other avenues to pursue,
我还得去跟进其它几条线索
I just haven't had the time to do it all.
我只是一直没时间把他们全部查完
- Tony, you got something? - Oh, yeah.
-Tony 你有什么发现 -哦 是的
You won't believe how hot Olivia Chandler is.
你绝对不敢相信Olivia Chandler有多火辣
Photos don't do her justice.
真人比照片好看多了
What's with her and Staff Sergeant Dunne?
她和Dunne上士是什么关系
Well, she claims they're only acquaintances
她声称她们只是
from A.A. meetings.
在A.A.会议上相识的
But I think it's more than that.
但我觉得不仅仅是这样
You said you had Dunne's credit card charges-- put them up.
你说你有Dunne的信用卡账单--把它放上来
-Why? -Trust me, put them up there.
-为什么 -相信我 放上来
All right, what are we looking for?
好了 我们在找什么
Well, if they're doing what I think they're doing,
好了 如果真如我所想象的那样
they're not doing it at her place.
他们是不会在她家里做那事的
And I don't think a rich housewife from Chevy Chase
我也不相信一个住在切维蔡斯有钱的家庭主妇
is dragging those long legs all the way down to Quantico.
会舍得挪动她尊贵的大腿跑去匡提科
Okay, wait. Hold on.
等等 就在这里
Chevy Chase Lodge.
切维蔡斯旅馆
There, there and there.
那里 那里和那里
Three nights, probably more.
三个晚上 或许还有更多
Take it down, McGee.
McGee 撤下来
Our 48 hours are up.
48小时的监禁时间到了
Yep.
是的
When do I get my truck back?
我什么时候能来开走我的车
I'm going to check out the Chevy Chase Lodge.
我去查一下切维蔡斯旅店
Book Private Cliff for the hit-and-run.
以交通肇事罪逮捕二等兵CLIFF
That's one case closed, another wide open.
这件案子结束了 另一个还不知道结果
Yes, dear, I understand.
是的 亲爱的 我了解
Do you?
你了解吗
-Do you even hear? -I hear you.
-你有认真在听吗 -我听着呢
No, no, no. I-I would never...
不 不 不 我永远不会
Well... oh, it's your mother's idea?
好吧...这是你妈妈的主意吗
Yes, it's my mother's idea!
是的 是她的意思
Why does that not surprise me?
为什么我对此一点也不惊讶
I have to go. I have a guest waiting.
我得挂了 有客人在等我
I do have a guest waiting.
真的有客人在等我
I'm not making that up.
我没有编
Uh... could you help me, please, sir?
额...先生 你能帮助我吗
Who is that? Hello?
这是谁 喂
Okay. I'll call you later.
好的 我一会再打给你
Fine! Like hell I will.
好 我宁愿去地狱也不想再打给你
You married?
你结婚了
Oh. No. Uh...
噢 没有. 额..
I'm a federal agent.
我是个联邦探员
DiNozzo.
DiNozzo.
Like to ask a few questions.
有几个问题要问你
All right, federal agent, ask away.
好吧 联邦探员 尽管问吧
Have you seen this man?
你见过这个人吗
Yeah.
是的
Yeah, sure.
没错
Sort of a regular.
算是个常客
Mmm?
嗯
So, does he come alone or...?
那么，他是一个人来还是...
Well, he'd like me to think that.
他倒是想让我这么认为
No, his friend never comes to the lobby.
不是 他的朋友从没来过前厅
He parks the car, and she goes directly to the room.
他停下车 她就直接进房间
So you got to figure, you know, one or both are married, right?
你自己就会去想 你知道 他们或者结了婚 对吧
Right. Yeah.
没错 是的
So you've never seen her?
所以你从来没见过她
Well, actually, I did the old
实际上 我有一次装作
knock-on-the-wrong-door routine one time.
敲错了门去看过
She look like this?
她长这样吗？
Yeah, that's her.
是的 这就是她
Woman like that, you do not forget.
这样的女人，你是永远不会忘记的
Right? I mean, can you imagine what one night with...
对吧 我是说 你能想象跟这样一位女士共度一晚...
I swear, the old witch is psychic.
我发誓 这老太婆绝对有通灵的能力
If I have so much as a thought of another woman...
每当我一想起其它的女人
You don't have to answer that.
你不必接这个电话
I have to. What...?!
我必须接 你想
...do you want?
干吗？
I got it. Good luck.
我了解了 好运
Just, do you need... if...
你需要..如果..
Take a card, sir.
拿张名片吧 先生
Thank you.
谢谢
Here.
给
Ah, always enjoy having a drink with you, Duck,
Duck,跟你一起喝酒总是很享受啊
but this isn't exactly on your way home from the symphony.
不过，这回不像是听完交响乐回家路过我这这么简单
What's on your mind?
你在想什么
Well, curiously, I was about to ask you that.
我正想问你同样的问题 我有些好奇
You've seemed... troubled
你看起来有些困惑不安
since you took that call in Autopsy yesterday.
自从你昨天在验尸房接了那个电话以后
Usually you're a master at hiding your feelings.
你通常都会很好的隐藏自己的感觉
That your professional opinion?
这是基于你专业的视角吗
The occupational hazard
跟一个侧写师一起工作的
of working with a profiler.
职业风险
Mmm.
嗯..
Yeah, I'm fine.
我很好
A little concerned about Carrie Clark.
有点担心Carrie Clark
The lawyer? Yeah, she's good.
律师 是的 她很不错
She got her client released without being charged.
她帮助她的代理人免于起诉
I sense a "but."
我察觉到你下一句 有个"但是"
Well, she does have a conscience.
她很有良心和道德感
Well, that's a good thing, isn't it?
这是件好事 不是吗
We learned some things about her client
我们了解到一些关于她的代理人的事情
that she may or may not have led us to.
她或多或少指引我们去的
Privileged information?
秘密的资料
Doc, I got to be careful how I handle this.
医生 我必须很小心的处理这件事情
For Carrie's sake.
保护Carrie
She could get disbarred.
不然她会被取消律师资格
Well, I know you, Jethro.
我知道你 Jethro
It sounds as if she's doing the right thing, as you are.
听起来她像在做正确的事 你也是
So how was the concert?
音乐会怎么样
Great. Tchaikovsky's Second.
非常好 柴可夫斯基第二号交响乐
I never realized that he wrote music for the movies.
我从来不知道他还给电影配过音乐
That's a car I've always had the hots for.
这是我非常迷恋的车
Maybe that's what I should get.
也许那才是我该开的
It's too old.
太老土了
You can't drive a car like that.
你不能开那样的车
It's not practical.
这不实用
That's the problem with you, McGeezer.
这就是你的问题 麦古板
Everything has to be practical.
所有的事都以实用为先
What...
我...
What I mean is, I've never known you
我的意思是 我从未见你
to do anything even a little risqué.
做出一点出格的事
Tony, you have no idea what I do on my time off.
Tony 你根本不知道我闲暇时在干什么
You know, that's true, I don't.
确实如此 我不知道
Why don't you tell me?
你为什么不跟我说呢
Share. Rock me. Sock me.
分享下喽  来啊  说啊
Well, there's Wendell Kaiser.
看  那是Wendell Kaiser
Wonder if Falls Church PD is tailing him, too.
猜猜如果福尔斯彻奇的警察也在跟踪他
Kaiser's their suspect.
Kaiser是他们的嫌犯
Is Kaiser going to church?
Kaiser准备去教堂
No. It's an A.A. meeting.
不 是一个AA聚会 【注：Alcoholics Anonymous，戒酒互助社】
They meet here every morning at this time.
他们每天早上都在这个时间见面
Wait, how do you know that?
等等 你怎么知道的
Anthony!
Anthony
What are you doing here?
你在这儿干嘛呢
Your meeting's not until tonight.
你的聚会应该在晚上啊
Reverend Miller, I, uh... - Bringing a new member?
Reverend Miller 我... - 带了个新成员吗
Um...
呃...
He's thinking about it. A little gun-shy.
他正在考虑要不要加入呢  有点疑神疑鬼
McGee, the Rev.
McGee  这是牧师
Please join us.
加入我们吧
It's a very safe place.
这是个非常安全的地方
All are welcome.
随时欢迎你
Tony, what's going on?
Tony  怎么回事
Do you have a drinking problem?
你酗酒了吗
No. No, I just...
不 不 我只是...
I joined this men's support group.
我加入了这个人的互助小组
Meets in the church hall two nights a week.
每周两晚在教堂大厅聚会
You serious?
认真的
Mm-hmm.
嗯
I know, it...
我知道 这...
it doesn't sound like me, but...
听起来并不像我 但是...
with the past year, I just...
过去这些年 我只是...
wanted to shake things up a little bit.
只是想振作一下
Meet some new people.
结识一些新的朋友
This guy at the gym told me about the group,
在健身房 他告诉了我这个组织
and I thought it sounded like a good idea.
我觉得听起来还不错
And it... it is, it's fun.
觉得...很有趣
The Rev drove me to Quantico the other morning.
有一天早上 牧师带我去了匡迪科
Interesting guy.
真是个有意思的人
He's helping me be less judgmental.
他帮我缓解评头论足的坏毛病
You know, Kaiser's going to be here for a while.
你知道的 Kaiser一会就要来了
We should get back.
我们得回去
Sergeant Dunne, Olivia Chandler and Wendell Kaiser
Dunne上士 Olivia Chandler以及Wendell Kaiser
all have one thing in common.
都有一个共同点
They all go to A.A. meetings.
他们都参加AA聚会
That's probably where they met.
他们也许是在那认识的
The sergeant and the trophy wife are lovers.
上士和花瓶妻子是情人关系
The desk clerk at the Chevy Chase Lodge
Chevy Chase旅馆的前台说
said that they were regulars.
他们都是常客
It's just like that movie Body Heat.
就像那部电影《体热》里的 【体热：赫特是佛罗里达的职业律师，遇上了已婚的社交名媛特纳，与之热恋 并共同密谋杀害她富有的丈夫】
William Hurt and Kathleen Turner.
威廉姆・赫特和凯瑟琳・特纳
God, she was really something, boss.
天呐 老大 她确实有问题啊
A head turner.
出乎意料
But I digress.
但我觉得有点离谱
Anyway, they were young lovers, just like these two,
不管怎么讲 他们是年轻的恋人 就像这俩人
and they wanted the rich husband's money
还图谋富豪丈夫的钱财
and him out of the way.
他们需要除掉那个富豪
On the other hand, you've got
另一方面 Wendell Kaiser
Wendell Kaiser, who's deep in debt to his bookie
输了很大笔钱给他的赌马经纪人
and needs him off his back.
他需要除掉那个经纪人
So they help each other out and switch murders.
所以他们互相帮助对方杀掉了想杀的人
While Kaiser was in New York,
当Kaiser在纽约时
Dunne killed the bookie with Olivia's help.
Dunne在Olivia的帮助下杀了赌马经纪人
She drove him. Her car was in the vicinity.
她负责开车  她的车就在附近
Who would ever suspect them?
谁又会怀疑他们呢
I mean, there's no connection, no motive.
我是说 根本没有联系也没有动机
Tomorrow Sergeant Dunne is going to deploy
第二天Dunne上士开始部署行动
and Olivia Chandler is off to Jamaica.
而Olivia Chandler去了牙买加
And I'm betting that while they're away,
我打赌当他们离开时
her husband's going to have a terrible accident
她的丈夫将会遭遇
at the hands of Mr. Kaiser here,
一起由Kaiser先生策划的严重事故
a man with whom he has no connection.
一个跟他完全没关系的人
Two murders, three solid alibis.
两起谋杀案 三个确凿的不在场证明
Interesting theory.
真是个有趣的解释
We know it's going to be a hard conspiracy for us to prove.
我们知道这是个很难证明的阴谋
We got to be careful-- it's not our case.
我们都要仔细些  不仅仅是案件
There's a way.
有一个办法
Find the weak link.
去找一些细微的联系
Hey, Kaiser.
嗨 Kaiser
You got a minute?
你有时间吗
Detective Dockry.
Dockry警探
I thought we were done.
我认为我们之间没什么可说的了
Look, I told you everything I know about Sullivan.
我把我知道的关于Sullivan的所有事都告诉你了
Yeah, well, something's come up.
是的 但是呢 又有一些新情况
Let's go to the station. We can talk about it.
我们去警局吧 聊聊新的情况
Nah, I'm not going anywhere.
呃 我哪也不去
Look, I had nothing to do with Sullivan's murder.
听着 我跟Sullivan的谋杀案一点关系都没有
I was in New York, man. You checked it out.
我当时在纽约 亲 你可以查的
You really want to do this in front of your friends?
你真的想在你朋友面前被带走吗
I'm not going anywhere with you.
我哪也不跟你去
We know about your buddy, Sergeant Dunne,
我们了解你的兄弟 Dunne上士
and his girlfriend.
还有他的女朋友
So let me explain how this works.
那就让我来解释下案件是怎么进行的
First suspect to flip on the others gets the deal.
首先 两方嫌疑人互通情报达成共识
Olivia Chandler?
Olivia Chandler
Hey, Gibbs.
嗨 Gibbs
DiNozzo told me that if you weren't at home
DiNozzo告诉我如果你不在家
I would probably find you here.
我没准能在这找到你
Have a seat.
坐吧
There a problem?
有什么问题吗
No, I...
没有 我...
just heard that Falls Church PD
只是听到一个福尔斯彻奇的警察
arrested my former client, Sergeant Dunne.
逮捕了我的前委托人 Dunne上士
Really?
是吗
Yeah, they booked him on multiple charges,
他们对他有多项指控
including conspiracy to commit murder and murder one.
包括串通谋杀和杀死一人
How'd they get him?
他们是怎么抓到他的
Apparently one of his coconspirators
很显然是他的其中一个同谋者
turned state's evidence.
将证据交给了警方
Sometimes... you get lucky.
有时候...你挺走运的
Mmm, is that what it was?
这就是走运
They got a warrant and cinched the case against Dunne
他们拿到了搜查令
when they found the murder weapon, a knife,
当在马桶水箱里找到了凶器---一把刀
in his bathroom toilet tank.
也就把这起谋杀案牢牢对准Dunne了
That's great.
太棒了
You okay?
你还好吗
Yeah.
是的
Why wouldn't I be? I did my job.
为什么不好呢  我完成了我的工作
I got Dunne off on the hit-and-run.
我在紧急关头抓住了Dunne
Yeah, you did it well.
你做的很好
Yes, and whatever happened to him after that,
是的 不管他之后发生了什么
it's not my concern.
都跟我没关系
Justice was served, all around.
正义终被伸张
Okay. Here you go.
好了 慢用
Care to join me for dinner?
介意跟我一起吃顿饭吗
Hmm, meat loaf and mashed potatoes?
肉饼和土豆泥
My favorite. I would be happy to.
我的最爱 我很乐意
Coming right up.
马上就好
Thanks, Elaine.
谢谢 Elaine
I think that you and me have a few things in common.
我觉得我们还是有一些共同点的
==GA字幕组== 翻译：入江之鲸 冰糖 一生为白 飞行猪 开心的小末 校对：流年打死不表白 关注海燕的毯子 lynhoo00 没抢到东西的蓉小张 K在苦逼找事做 伽尘师太 字幕特效/时间轴：闹不闹得住菇 无限Boss爱渣  压制：米兰伯爵
==GA字幕组== 翻译：入江之鲸 冰糖 一生为白 飞行猪 开心的小末 校对：流年打死不表白 关注海燕的毯子 lynhoo00 没抢到东西的蓉小张 K在苦逼找事做 伽尘师太 字幕特效/时间轴：闹不闹得住菇 无限Boss爱渣  压制：米兰伯爵
阿鲸-要认认真真地学习工作和生活~ 冰糖-希望下雨的日子赶快过去吧^^ 小白-纽约竟然下雪了，我要回深圳过冬 小末-小末不要mg嫁给别人 飞行猪-Tony每次都灵感爆发啊！ 伯爵-我也想跟Boss一起吃土豆泥肉饼（这玩意吃不胖吗？Boss的肌肉哪里来的？） 毯子-祝贺小末末拿到奖学金！小麦和Delilah感情很稳定啊~ K-谁娶到那个旅店老婆谁倒霉 佳晨-热哭的广东终于降温了 流年-麦呆和眼镜兄还真挺八卦 lynhoo00-Gibbs和那女律师虾米关系？Tony为啥关心人家离婚没？ 蓉蓉-弱弱的觉得女律师不错
阿鲸-要认认真真地学习工作和生活~ 冰糖-希望下雨的日子赶快过去吧^^ 小白-纽约竟然下雪了，我要回深圳过冬 小末-小末不要mg嫁给别人 飞行猪-Tony每次都灵感爆发啊！ 伯爵-我也想跟Boss一起吃土豆泥肉饼（这玩意吃不胖吗？Boss的肌肉哪里来的？） 毯子-祝贺小末末拿到奖学金！小麦和Delilah感情很稳定啊~ K-谁娶到那个旅店老婆谁倒霉 佳晨-热哭的广东终于降温了 流年-麦呆和眼镜兄还真挺八卦 lynhoo00-Gibbs和那女律师虾米关系？Tony为啥关心人家离婚没？ 蓉蓉-弱弱的觉得女律师不错